<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Defs>
    <ThingDef ParentName="ResourceBase">
        <thingClass>ThingWithComps</thingClass>
        <defName>BOR_Neutronium</defName>
        <label>neutronium</label>
        <description>An exotic form of matter composed of neutrons in tight gridlock. While naturally-occuring neutronium maintains this density through its own gravity, one must commit massive quantities of energy in order to form and maintain neutron matter planetside. On its own it is useless to you and dangerous to store, but alongside solar, quasar, and tenebral tech it can be used to transmute elements, synthesize goods, and equip armies. You can form neutronium into virtually anything!\n\nNeutronium is the foundation of neutronosynthesis ("n-synthesis"), the process of turning stuff into neutronium, storing it, then turning neutronium into better stuff. Most of the neutronium used in final products is lost to radiation, making n-synthesis a rather wasteful process. N-synthesis requires special infrastructure - refineries, synthesizers, storage, and pipes - made from materials at least as strong as sunsteel. Some high-tech items are only possible through n-synthesis. Improperly storing neutronium can be catastrophic; the decompression alone is enough to level entire cities.</description>
        <graphicData>
            <texPath>BOR/Things/Item/Resource/neutronium</texPath>
            <graphicClass>Graphic_StackCount</graphicClass>
        </graphicData>
        <resourceReadoutAlwaysShow>true</resourceReadoutAlwaysShow>
        <resourceReadoutPriority>First</resourceReadoutPriority>
        <soundInteract>Standard_Pickup</soundInteract>
        <soundDrop>Standard_Drop</soundDrop>
        <useHitPoints>false</useHitPoints>
        <thingCategories>
            <li>ResourcesRaw</li>
        </thingCategories>
        <stackLimit>5000</stackLimit>
        <smallVolume>true</smallVolume>
        <drawGUIOverlay>true</drawGUIOverlay>
        <deepCommonality>0</deepCommonality>
        <tickerType>Never</tickerType>
        <comps>
            <li Class="CompProperties_Forbiddable" />
            <li Class="CompProperties_Glower">
                <glowRadius>2</glowRadius>
                <glowColor>(145,131,83,0)</glowColor>
            </li>
        </comps>
        <statBases>
            <MarketValue>5</MarketValue>
            <Mass>0.001</Mass>
            <Flammability>0.0</Flammability>
            <DeteriorationRate>0.0</DeteriorationRate>
            <Beauty>15</Beauty>
        </statBases>
        <tradeability>None</tradeability>
        <thingSetMakerTags>
            <li>RewardStandardMidFreq</li>
        </thingSetMakerTags>
    </ThingDef>
</Defs>